WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Hey, listen, you gotta
get back in bed now, okay?
It's the middle of the night there.
- Can you...
- Where's Daddy?
Can you give the phone
to Grammy, please?
- I want Daddy.
- Ca... Cameron?
- Hey, Cam?
- Where's Daddy?
- Cameron?
- Daddy.
Cameron!
He wants to talk to you.
Yeah. Oh. Hey, buddy. How are you?
- Good!
- We love you.
We'll see you tomorrow!
I'm gonna help you.
I don't want you to go.
Maybe you can come to L.A.
Buongiorno.
Here she is. The new diva of Palermo.
- Do you want some coffee?
- I'd love some. Thanks.
- Hugo.
- Okay.
So, how was Niccolò?
I... I mean, the whole
night was like a dream.
We just wanted you to
have the perfect send-off.
Oh, send-off. What?
We have to leave Villa Pisano
and bring you back to Taormina.
Oh.
You know, I just wish
I could grab you all
and fold you up in my
trunk and take you with me.
- Aww.
- I do.
Well, we could probably all fit.
That's true.
It's a wonderful thing to make a...
a new friend so late in life.
Late in life?
It's... it's a French
saying. "Tard dans la vie."
- Oh.
- Late. Yes, it's, a...
- Oh, okay.
- French.
- French saying.
- So many French sayings.
Hey, has anyone seen Portia?
- Is she here?
- No.
Did anyone see her at the party?
She's probably traipsing
through the fields
with Jack somewhere.
This is my luck, you know?
My bad luck with assistants.
They become my boss.
I'm taking orders from them
and they're bossing me around.
And they, you know, start
stealing my medications
and... and then they disappear.
This is just how it goes with me.
What are you doing?
I... I can't find my
phone. Where's my phone?
How should I know?
Well, I was charging it all night.
It was right here.
- So I...
- I'm sure you'll find it.
It's gotta be somewhere.
Just come back to bed.
I need my phone. I need to call Tanya.
It's fine. I texted my uncle.
It's all good.
Come on.
It's all gonna be fine.
My phone, it's so weird.
Maybe you left it at the bar.
No, I definitely had it last night
'cause I was trying to
find you on Instagram
and I couldn't find you.
I don't do that shit.
Not even Instagram?
Oh, Dio. Buongiorno.
Valentina...
Apparently, he just
got super ragey at work.
Ragey? Adam?
Yeah. He just lost...
he threw a... a yogurt
at his assistant's face.
He got fired 'cause he threw a yogurt?
- Jesus.
- Yes. You can't throw
a yogurt at someone's face.
It's his assistant. Who cares?
I ran into his wife at
the gym. She's awful.
Oh, my God.
Two kids in private school.
I mean, his family can help
them a little bit, but...
Christ. When did the
world become run by nuns?
I mean, you're not even supposed
to succeed anymore, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Cause if you succeed,
oh, shit, you might make
someone else feel bad.
You might cause harm
to all the sad losers in the world.
You're an idiot.
- Hey.
How'd you sleep?
Fine. Um, Dad?
Yeah?
I need 50,000 euros.
Fifty thousand euros?
What for?
Oh, no, not for that girl.
Well, forget it.
I have all the bank account information,
so you can just call your accountant
and have him wire the money.
Yeah. Sure. I'll just
call him right now. Yeah.
Gimme the...
No.
- What?
- You can make someone's life.
Fifty thousand euros? And...
and you just met this girl,
- like, what, three days ago?
- So what?
Come on, Albie. Get real.
Lots of people need help in the world.
I'm not an NGO.
You don't need it. It's nothing to you.
No, it's nothing to you 'cause
you don't work for money.
It's pretty much nothing to you.
I mean, what? You're just gonna
go through life trying to rescue
every desperate girl you come across?
Maybe. Yeah.
Well, good luck with that.
Don't expect me to subsidize.
Think of it as a karmic payment.
- A karmic payment?
- Yeah.
- For what?
- For all the shit you've done.
Ten thousand euros.
- Are we negotiating?
- No. I don't know. I mean...
What... She doesn't need 50,000 euros.
- Yes, she does.
- Why does she need it?
There's a dude stalking her.
You saw him. And she's
stuck and... Whatever.
I just... Fifty thousand
dollars. I can't. I could never...
- not in good conscience ever...
- Conscience?
Now you have a conscience? Over this?
Just do it. Just give it.
And then what? Are you gonna have
some kind of relationship
with this girl?
Why not, you know? I like her.
We've been talking about
her coming to visit L.A.
Come on, man. Albie. I mean...
How are you gonna make it in life
- if you're this big a mark?
- I'm not a mark.
I'll help you out with Mom.
Give me 50...
and I'll help you with Mom.
- How are you gonna help me?
- I don't know.
I'll tell her how sorry you are
and how this whole trip,
all you could think about was her,
and how it seems like
you've really changed.
Yadda, yadda.
You would do that?
- Morning.
What are we talking about?
- Nothing.
I had a dream that we went
to visit our relatives.
They turned out to
be a bunch of banshees
and chased us out of town.
Ah. Wow.
Okay.
- Ciao.
- Ah, no?
- No.
Ah, okay.
Ah!
- Sì.
- Grazie, grazie.
Salvatore.
Salvatore. Salvato...
Scusa, eh.
Grazie.
Hello? Hello?
What are you doing?
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
You know, I came in here last night,
you know, and I saw this photo.
And I thought I dreamt
it, but here it is.
I mean, who is this?
Steve.
Oh.
He worked on a dude ranch I stumbled on
when I was bumming around
in my aspiring Kerouac days.
We used to go fly-fishing
and drop acid together.
What ever happened to him?
Do you know? I don't really know.
Lost touch. Haven't
spoken to him in decades.
I mean, my God. He looks just like Greg.
- Greg?
- My husband.
Only he has hair.
Well, the resemblance is uncanny.
Well, we're heading out.
We need to be at the
dock in half an hour.
Matteo is staying back, unfortunately,
but he wanted to say goodbye.
- Arrivederci, Tanya.
- Oh. My God, Matteo.
Buona fortuna.
- Oh.
- Buona fortuna.
Hey.
- Shall we?
- Oh. Yeah.
He's really crying.
Yes. Italians, they tend
to get a little overwrought.
What's wrong?
You fucked him.
- What?
- I know what you did.
You fucked him to get back at me,
but I did nothing wrong.
- Are you okay?
- I know you did something.
I didn't.
You're lying. You're not a good liar.
Because I'm not lying and I don't lie.
You just called him
an idiot at breakfast.
That was the tell. You
would not have done that
if something hadn't
happened between you.
- That doesn't make any sense.
- Stop fucking with me, Harper.
I can forgive you, but
just be honest with me.
- I saw you at the fucking bar.
- What bar?
You know the bar.
I was in the water and
you guys were doing shots
and flirting and
whispering to each other.
And then I come up here and
the fucking door is latched?
- Why was the door latched?
- I don't know.
Yeah, right.
I don't know. You're
reading into it, okay?
It... It's not like you
found a condom on the couch.
The difference is, I didn't do anything!
Did I?
- How do I know?
- Because I fucking told you.
You asked me so I told you.
I told you the whole truth.
Well, I'm telling you I
didn't do anything, okay?
Haven't I always been honest with you?
Yeah. But you're lying now.
- Ethan, fuck off.
- Just be honest with me.
Just be honest with me.
Just tell me what happened.
I can't move on from this
until you tell me exactly the truth.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, we did shots at the bar.
- Mm-hmm.
- And...
And, yeah, I was really mad at you
because of the hookers and the condom
- and the whole situation.
- And then?
And then...
And then he said, "Let's go upstairs."
The night before at dinner,
under the table, he...
he kept touching my leg
or something. I don't know.
I was drunk, obviously.
S...
So we went upstairs.
I let him in the room.
He latched the door.
And then he kissed me.
But that was it, okay? That was all.
You came up right away.
He went through the connecting door.
And he kissed me for like two seconds.
It was nothing. And I was drunk.
And I'm not even
attracted to him anyway.
He's disgusting, okay? It
was a drunk, stupid nothing.
I regretted it immediately,
okay? That was it.
So it wasn't for the hat?
The hat?
You said you came up
here for a fucking hat.
It's not funny.
I know.
No, it wasn't for the hat.
But it was nothing, okay?
It was a drunk, dumb nothing.
It was less than nothing.
And the real issue is that
you're not attracted to me anyway.
You don't want have sex
with me. You make up excuses.
You'd rather watch porn.
That is the problem.
Not Cameron kissing me for two seconds.
You're still lying to me.
- I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
I came up, like, ten minutes after you
and you're telling me
that all you did was kiss?
You're minimizing it.
N... No. We went up the wrong path.
- We were drunk.
- Bullshit. Fucking bullshit.
- It's not bullshit.
- Stop bullshitting me, please.
Ethan, I swear to God.
All right. You didn't fuck
him, but what happened?
Did you suck his dick? Did you blow him?
- No.
- Did he get his dick out?
No. What?
You're lying to me.
I... I told you what happened, so, I...
All right. I don't know
what the fuck happened,
but one thing that I do
know is he tried to fuck you.
Where are you going?
Coming!
Oh, hey, Ethan. What's going on?
Where the fuck is Cameron?
Um, he's at the beach, taking a swim.
Is everything okay?
Cameron!
Hey! Hey!
Hey, buddy, what's up?
- Are you trying to fuck my wife?
- What?
Are you trying to fuck my wife, huh?
- Are you?
- I have no idea
what you're fucking talking about, man.
Is that why you invited us out here
on this dumb fucking vacation?
Dude. Do you think I invited you here
- so I could fuck your wife?
- Why do you do this, man?
'Cause I make more money than you now?
- Jesus Christ!
- To make yourself feel better
- about yourself, huh?
- No. No, look.
- We're friends, man.
- Don't fucking touch me.
I'm happy for you, buddy.
- We're friends?
- Yeah.
We are not friends.
This is not some girl
that I have a crush on.
It's my fucking wife.
- Come on.
- Friends don't try to fuck
each other's fucking wives, asshole!
You're fucking crazy.
Fuck.
Hey, let him go! Let him go!
What the fuck?
Hey, hey, hey!
Get the fuck off me, man!
Get outta here, man. Come on. Enough.
I'm still just confused about
where my phone went, you know?
'Cause like...
I got a feeling you'll find it.
Well, I kinda need it now.
I'm here for work,
and Tanya's my boss, and
I have to call her and...
Yeah, well, she can't
talk to you now anyway
'cause she's on the boat.
She is?
They're heading back to Taormina.
But what about me? How
am I supposed to get back?
Well, I'm driving ya.
I thought, you know, you'd like that.
It's our last day together.
I wanna show you around the island.
Want you to be satisfied, don't I?
All right. I'm gonna take a shit...
and then I'm gonna get you a drink
'cause you need to tranquillo.
All right?
What a life you have. I
mean, this boat, your villa...
Oh, my God, everything
you have is a work of art.
So many incredible palazzi in Sicily
are in a terrible state.
We spend half our lives raising money
to keep these historic estates
from falling into ruin,
don't we, Didier, darling?
I do the same in the
south of France, you know.
- Noblesse oblige.
- Yeah. And, you know,
there aren't enough people out there
that are worried about old buildings.
We're here on Earth such a short time,
but our houses live on.
We must be good stewards.
So glad you agree.
Oh, jeez. Wait, hold on.
Don't normally get
reception out on the water.
Hello?
Portia? Portia... I can't
hear... Hold on a second. Hold on.
Excuse me.
And what number is this, anyway?
Uh, it's... it's Jack's.
I lost my phone and I
have this weird feeling
that he... that he took it or something.
Oh. Yeah, well, I wouldn't be surprised.
Listen, Portia, I know
you really like him,
but...
... the other night I was
walking around the villa and...
Well...
I saw Jack and his uncle and, you know,
they were, like... they were,
like, naked and stuff like that.
They w... They were naked? Doing what?
Well...
... he was kinda fucking his uncle.
What?
I didn't have the heart
to tell you before.
- Portia? Portia?
- Yeah.
Yeah. I... I f...
I feel like something bad is happening.
- What do you mean, "bad"?
- I don't know.
I just have this really weird feeling
that something bad is gonna happen.
To you or to me?
Jack got really drunk last night
and he was saying how like,
um, Quentin has no money,
and he almost lost his house,
and he's about to come
into this giant windfall
or something, and Jack is helping him.
That doesn't make any sense.
Look, I... I'm on his yacht right now.
- He has money.
- Yeah.
I just have this... this
really creepy feeling right now.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Something
weird did happen last night!
- What?
- I was in Quentin's bedroom,
and there was this photo
of a guy on his desk.
And it looked just like Greg.
Greg? There was a picture of Greg?
Well, it couldn't be Greg.
I mean, he doesn't know
any gay guys in Sicily.
But then he did insist
that we come to Sicily.
The prenup. The prenup. The prenup!
What... what about the prenup?
If we divorce, he
gets basically nothing.
But, if...
- If what?
- If I...
- Die?
- Oh.
- Oh, my God.
- Um, Tanya.
- Uh...
Portia, meet me in Taormina.
We gotta get the fuck outta here.
Yeah. Uh, okay. Uh... You're gonna be...
You're gonna be fine
though, Tanya, okay?
I... I really feel like
we're just overthinking
- this whole thing. And...
- Oi!
Sh...
Portia?
Um...
Was that an international call?
'Cause that... that costs me money.
I need to get back to Taormina,
like... like right away.
Your flight's not till tomorrow.
It's our last day together. But...
- Yeah. Um...
- Why are you acting funny?
Yeah. I feel like I...
I need to get back now.
- Yeah.
You'll get back. There's no rush.
Come on. I wanna show you Sicily.
Okay. Um...
Yeah.
Hello.
How was Portia?
Has Hades carried her
off into the Underworld?
So, uh, how much longer to Taormina?
Just a few hours.
Enjoy the Ionian Sea
while you still can.
Ethan.
Come here. Sit down.
- Hey.
- Hi.
You okay? You haven't
really seemed like yourself
the past couple of days.
Work stuff?
What is it?
You wanna know?
Yeah.
I think...
You think what?
Cameron and Harper.
Cameron and Harper, what?
Maybe something happened.
I don't think you have
anything to worry about.
I mean, we never really know
what goes on in people's minds
or what they do, right?
You spend every second with somebody
and there's still this
part that's a mystery.
You know?
You don't have to know everything
to love someone.
A little mystery?
It's kinda sexy.
I'm a mystery to myself.
Honestly, I surprise
myself all the time.
I think you just... you just...
do whatever you have to do
not to feel like a victim of life.
You know?
Just use your imagination.
Have you been over there
yet, to Isola Bella?
I really wanna go before we leave.
It looks so pretty.
Come on. Walk with me.
Well, now that we're here,
c... can we get off the boat?
Oh, well,
I thought we'd have
our last dinner onboard.
No, I... I really just
wanna get back to my hotel.
Oh, no. Are you bored of us?
- No. No, no, no. I...
- The thing is
we're about as close as
we can get on a big boat.
The good news is that
Niccolò, your paramour,
is arriving this evening
on a little dinghy
and he's going to escort
you personally to the shore.
Just me and him?
One last rendezvous?
What's not fun about that?
Ah.
Hey.
Ciao.
Grazie.
Um...
- Um...
- Hmm.
Okay.
Sì.
Ah.
Mm.
Ciao.
Rocco.
Grazie, Valentina.
Sì.
Hey.
Um...
Huh?
Hmm.
Um...
Eh.
Mm...
Hmm?
- Huh?
- Eh.
Huh?
Hey.
Ciao.
See? Told you they wouldn't tow it.
Can you just cut the shit,
like, have I been kidnapped
or what's... what's going on?
What? What are you on about? No.
Like, I... I know you
stole my phone, so...
Are you mental?
Please, can you just tell me the truth?
I know you've been lying to me
and I know Quentin isn't your uncle.
Wh... Yes, he is. Wh... I...
Yeah? So you fuck your uncle?
Wha... Fu...
Well, I was gonna show you
around the island, but...
I'm not really in the mood now.
Guess I'll just drive you back.
I can just... I can just get a cab.
It takes a couple of hours.
You can't afford a cab.
Anyway, me uncle made
me promise to drive ya.
You don't want me to get
in trouble now, do ya?
Just let me do me job. Yeah?
How am I your job?
Like, you've just been,
like, assigned to me this...
- Oi!
- Oh.
Just leave it alone.
Yeah?
Okay.
Oh. Shit!
This boat is huge.
Yes. Hey. Hi. Yeah.
- Hi. Okay.
- Buona sera, signora.
Hi. Hey. Do you speak English?
- No.
- No inglese? Okay.
Hey. Do you know these gays?
- Do you know these gays?
- Gay?
I know it sounds crazy,
but my husband, he knows Quentin.
See, he brought me to
Sicily and then he left,
so he could have an
alibi. And then these gays,
they take me off to Palermo
and then they set me up with
this guy who's in the mafia
and he's coming here I... I think
to try to throw me off the boat.
They're going to do
Greg's dirty work for him
because he's gonna
pay them with my money
so they can decorate
their houses or some shit.
I may... may be paranoid,
but I need you to drive me in the boat,
drive the boat to the shore.
Please?
These gays, they're trying to murder me.
Can...
- Mi capisci?
- Sì.
- Mi... Yeah?
Oh. Yeah?
Uh...
- Eh.
- What?
- You're gay?
- Sì.
Tutti.
Oh, my God.
I actually had that thought, too.
Yeah. He's got that red face thing.
- It looks a little swollen.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Hold on one second.
- Hi.
- Good evening. Welcome.
Um... Dinner for two,
I think. Right, two?
Yeah. I guess, yeah.
Mia, Mia!
- Hey, can we sit here? Perfect.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- There you go.
Oh.
- Guys.
- Hey.
Hey.
- Sure.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Hey.
- There you are.
How are you?
- Did you get my text?
- No.
Oh, I just texted you.
You guys gonna eat alone?
- It's our last night. Come on.
- Thanks. Yeah.
Hey, uh, can we get two more
- place settings for here?
- Thank you.
- Certainly.
- Thanks.
Oh, and a bottle of your best champagne.
- I'll go get that.
- It's so nice out here.
Wow.
Okay.
Scusi. Scusi.
- Mm-hmm?
- I got the job. Singing here.
- Oh, congratulations.
- Grazie.
Grazie. Grazie mille. Grazie!
- Grazie. Grazie, grazie.
- Prego.
I did it.
You did what?
My karmic payment.
Money's transferred. It's all handled.
But let's not make it
a big deal.
I'd like to pretend it
never happened, okay?
And although it's not why I did it,
maybe at some point, you can
put in a word for me with your mother.
I already did.
Yeah?
Sweet girl.
You know, she could be my granddaughter.
But, uh, when she hugged me just now,
I got a little aroused.
- God.
- No, no, it's a...
a natural reaction.
Our Achilles' heel is an Achilles' cock.
It's like a... a Greek curse.
Um, I wanna... Can I pass on
dinner tonight? I'm gonna...
I love you. Thank you.
Love you.
Oh.
What was that all about?
Guys, I just wanted to say,
this has been an amazing trip.
When some...
... flunky in the housing office at Yale
decided to put me and
E in the same dorm room,
who would've known that
all these years later,
we'd still be in each other's lives?
I think that's pretty cool, man.
And, Harper, it has been fantastic
to finally get to know you properly.
And, baby...
thanks for putting up with me.
- I love you.
Cheers, guys. To friendship.
To travel. To the good life.
- Cheers.
Next year, the Maldives.
Hmm.
More scuba, less pasta.
I have some good news.
What?
Check your bank account.
Brava.
Not a lasagna fan?
I'm distracted.
Well, Niccolò is quite distracting.
You're a lucky woman.
We're all very jealous.
Very, very.
Well, thanks for the introduction.
I wanted you to have the
most magical time in Sicily.
It was the least I could do.
Here he is.
Aw.
Well, whenever you're ready
Niccolò can take you back to Taormina.
Do I... Wait... But what about Didier
and wh... what's-his-face?
I mean, don't they have to
go back to the hotel, too?
No, Didier and Hugo are
sleeping on the boat.
So, it'll just be you and Niccolò.
Quite romantic in the moonlight.
Would you like to go?
No. No. No, no.
I would like another
glass of white wine.
We've got all the time in the world.
Ethan?
What's gonna happen to us?
Thank you.
Hey.
You answered. How are you?
I miss you.
Listen, I can't talk right now, okay?
But, um, I guess, just... call
me when you get back into town.
Yeah, yeah, I will, for sure.
- Bye.
- Okay. Bye.
Why did we stop?
Jack?
Where are we?
I thought you said you were
gonna take me back to Taormina.
We're not going to Taormina.
Huh?
This is Catania. The
airport is just that way.
Do you want my advice?
Don't go to the hotel.
Don't wait around.
Just get on your flight tomorrow,
get the fuck out of Sicily.
All right?
These people are powerful.
You don't wanna fuck with 'em.
Look, I know you're smart, all right?
Smarter than me. So...
just don't be stupid.
Wait, wait, wait.
Well, it's about that
time. Wouldn't you say?
All right. I g... I have
to use the powder room.
Well, you know where it is.
Tanya?
Uh. Yeah?
Is everything all right?
- Yeah.
- Tanya.
- Tanya?
- Yeah.
- Tanya.
- Yeah. In a minute.
Tanya, is everything all right?
- Yeah.
- Tanya?
In a minute.
You... This isn't a bathroom, is it?
It's a bedroom. Do you need some help?
Tanya?
- Yeah?
- Can we come in?
Yeah.
Should we have a little talk?
Is Greg having an affair?
Tell me, I know you know. I...
Tell me!
What?
Oh, shit.
Wait a minute. No,
wait a minute. I can't.
Can I get there? Can I?
I can't get off.
Oh, I can't.
You've got this.
Hey.
Portia?
Hi.
Hey.
Uh, where's your, uh,
dad and grandfather?
Oh, they're just over there.
Yeah.
Where's your boss?
She's not answering her phone right now.
Oh, did you hear that one of
the guests drowned at the hotel?
Do you know who?
No, it was crazy.
They found a bunch of dead
bodies on a yacht, too.
How was Palermo?
Not great.
And what about the guy?
- He's deranged.
- Oh.
Yeah. And what about the girl,
- you know, that...
- Oh, yeah.
She played me.
Oh.
So... Uh...
- Can I get your number?
- Yeah.
- Sure.
- Oh, cool.
You could just put it in.
Yeah, and give me yours.
Yeah.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -